ABOUT

Enthusiastic, highly motivated, organised, communicative, focused on aim .Loves new technology and has been interested in computer technology since has been a teenager. Has lived in the United Kingdom since 2020 and has worked in the logistics industry for over two years.

CONTACT



natalia.sokolowska12@gmail.com



07395 830106



nataliasokolowska.co.uk



Long Eaton, Nottingham

EDUCATION



Zespol szkol nr 5 Lublin Polish Matura(equivalent to A Level) 2016



Pitman Training Peterborough Web Developer Diploma Advanced Software and Web Developer Diploma

NATALIA SOKOLOWSKA

WEB DEVELOPER

OBJECTIVE

Quality-focused and results-driven professional seeking a position as a web developer.

EXPERIENCE

FULFILMENT ASSOCIATE/PROCESS GUIDE

Amazon UK service

(17/07/2021-16/02/2023)

I was responsible for getting orders ready for customers relying on Amazon services, managing teams over shift day, day to day issue solving and reporting, keeping work flow well and communicating with team leaders and managers.

WAREHOUSE OPERATIVE/ADMIN

XPO Logistics

(26/06/2020-09/05/2021)

I was responsible for preparing orders for customers relying on the Ted Baker brand, administrating orders, checking all information, and responding to questions from customers.

MANAGER

Kakadu Studio Koloru, Poland (01/07/2019-30/03/2020)

The main aim of this position was getting customers happy with our products and helping them with decisions.

Additionally, I was preparing the new team to be ready for taking on my responsibilities as customer advisors.

Administrating, communicating with a bookkeeper, social media and helping with creating a web site.